本字幕由 极地影视 修正制作
欢迎访问 www.jddy.net
寒冷的夜晚伴随着山雨她出生了
Born of cold and Winter air And mountain rain combining,
不畏严寒的肆虐
This icy force both foul and fair.
冰封的心等待着挖掘
Has a frozen heart worth mining.
寒冷剔透的心
Cut through the heart, Cold and Clear.
为了爱而不畏恐惧
Strike for love And Strike for fear.
一双善于发现美丽的眼睛
See the beauty Sharp and Sheer.
打破寒冰结境
Split the ice apart.
融化冰封之心
And break the frozen heart.
哈!嚯!注意脚下!起!
Hup! Ho! Watch your step! Let it go!
美丽又动人!
Beautiful! Powerful!
寒冷又危险!
Dangerous! Cold!
冰的魔法无法被掌控
Ice has a magic Can't be controlled.
不害怕一个人 也不害怕十个人
Stronger than one, Stronger than ten.
一百个人也不放在眼里
Stronger than a hundred men!
寒冷的夜晚伴随着山雨她出生了
Born of cold and winter air And mountain rain combining.
不畏严寒的肆虐
This icy force both Foul and Fair.
冰封的心等待着挖掘
Has a frozen heart worth mining.
寒冷剔透的心
Cut through the heart, Cold and Clear.
为了爱而不畏恐惧
Strike for love and strike for fear.
美丽与危险共存
There's beauty and there's Danger here.
打破寒冰结境
Split the ice apart!
融化冰封之心
Beware the frozen heart.
快来呀 小斯!
Come on, Sven!
埃尔莎
Elsa. Psst
埃尔莎!
Elsa!
快醒来
Wake up. Wake up. Wake up.
安娜 回你的床上去
Anna, go back to sleep.
我不能 天是醒的 所以我也是醒的
I just can't. The sky's awake, so I'm awake,
我们来玩游戏吧
so we have to play.
和自己玩去吧
...Go play by yourself.
你想堆雪人吗
Do you want to build a snowman?
来吧 来吧 来吧
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
来点魔法! 来点魔法!
Do the magic! Do the magic!
准备好了没?
Ready? Uhhm...
太神奇啦!
This is amazing!
看好了!
Watch this!
嘿 我是喜欢温暖拥抱的雪宝
Hi, I'm Olaf and I like warm hugs.
我爱你 雪宝
I love you, Olaf.
好 接住我! -接住啦!
Al'right. Catch me! - Gotcha!
再来一次! -等下!
Again! Wait!
慢一点!
Slow down!
安娜!
Anna!
安娜?
Anna?
妈!爸爸!
Mama! Papa!
没事的 安娜 我陪着你
You Ok, Anna. I Got you.
埃尔莎 你做了什么?你又乱用魔法了!
Elsa, what have you done? This is getting out of hand!
这是个意外 对不起 安娜
It was an accident. I'm sorry, Anna.
她冰冷的 -我知道我们得去哪
- She's ice cold. - I know where we have to go.
冰?
Ice?
快点 小斯!
Faster, Sven!
小斯!
Sven!
请帮帮我们!
Please... Help!
救救我们的女儿!
My daughter!
他是国王!
He is the King!
巨魔?
Trolls...?
嘘 我要听听发生了什么
Shush. I'm trying to listen.
小可爱们 我要留下你们
Cuties. I'm gonna keep you.
陛下!
Your Majesty!
与生俱来的力量还是诅咒?
Born with the powers or cursed?
生下来就有的 而且越来越强大
Born. And they're getting stronger.
好在没有击中她的心
You are lucky it wasn't her heart.
击中心的话就没那么容易改变了
The heart is not so easily changed,
击中头的话还有办法
But the head can be persuaded.
做你必须做的
Do what you must.
我建议我们消除她身上所有的魔力
I recommend we remove all magic,
为了安全连着这段记忆也一起
even memories of magic to be safe...
别担心 我会留下快乐的记忆
But don't worry, I'll leave the fun.
她会没事的
She will be okay.
她会忘记我有的魔力?
But she won't remember I have powers?
这样是最好的 -听着 埃尔莎
- It's for the best. - Listen to me, Elsa,
你的魔力只会越来越强大
your power will only grow.
你会发现它的美好
There is beauty in it...
同时也伴随着危险
But also great danger.
你一定要学会控制它
You must learn to control it.
恐惧会成为你的敌人
Fear will be your enemy.
不 我们会保护她 她能做到的 相信我
No. We'll protect her. She can learn to control it. I'm sure.
在这之前
Until then,
我们会锁上大门 减少仆人
we'll lock the gates. We'll reduce the staff.
限制她与人的交往
We will limit her contact with people
让她的魔力不被人所知
and keep her powers hidden from everyone...
包括安娜
including Anna.
埃尔莎?
Elsa?
你想堆雪人吗
Do you want to build a snowman?
来吧我们一起来玩吧
Come on let's go and play.
好久没见到你了 出来吧
I never see you anymore. Come out the door.
你就像消失了一样
It's like you've gone away.
我们曾是最好的玩伴
We used to be best buddies.
现在却变了 你能告诉我原因吗
And now we're not. I wish you would tell me why.
你想堆雪人吗
Do you want to build a snowman?
玩什么都可以呀
It doesn't have to be a snowman.
离我远点 安娜
Go away, Anna.
好吧 拜拜
...Okay bye.
带上手套就没事了 看到了吗...
The gloves will help. See...
隐藏它 -别去感受
- Conceal it. - Don't feel it.
别显现出来
Don't let it show.
你想堆雪人吗
Do you want to build a snowman?
还是绕着走廊骑自行车?
Or ride our bike around the hall?
我觉得这里的同伴太少了..
I think some company is overdue...
我开始和墙上的画像讲话
I've started talking to the pictures on the walls.
坚持住 琼
Hang in there, Joan.
这些空房子让人觉得有些寂寞
It gets a little lonely all these empty rooms.
凝视着时间滴答滴答
Just watching the hours tick by.
我很害怕 它变的越来越强大
I'm scared. It's getting stronger.
不安只会让情况变糟
Getting upset only makes it worse.
冷静下来
Calm down.
别碰我 我怕伤害了你
No. Don't touch me. Please. I don't want to hurt you.
两周后再见
See you in two weeks.
你要走了吗 -你会没事的 埃尔莎
- Do you have to go? - You'll be fine, Elsa.
埃尔莎?
Elsa?
请回答我 我知道你在里面
Please, I know you're in there.
人们都在找你
People are asking where you've been,
他们说要有勇气 而我在尝试
They say have courage and I'm trying to...
我在外面等你 让我进来吧
I'm right out here for you. Just let me in.
我们只拥有彼此了
We only have each other.
只有你和我
It's just you and me.
我们该怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
你想堆雪人吗
Do you want to build a snowman?
三年后
欢迎来到安瑞戴尔 谢谢你!
Welcome to Arendelle! Thank you, Sir!
注意脚下 大门马上要打开了
Watch your Steps please. The Gates Will opening Soon.
我一定要穿这个吗
Why do I have to wear this?
因为女王的时代已经来临了
Because the Queen has come of age.
今天是加冕日!
It's Coronation Day!
跟我有什么关系
That's not my fault.
你想要什么 小斯? -给我点吃的!
- What do you want, Sven? - Give me a snack!
魔法单词是什么? 请!
What's the magic word? Please!
A..a....a....a! 分享!
A..a... a... a! Share!
不敢相信他们终于打开那些门了
I can't believe they're finally opening up the gates!
而且打开一整天哦!
And for a whole day!
快 珀西!
Faster, Persi!
安瑞戴尔 我们最神秘的交易拍档
Ah, Arendelle, our most mysterious trade partner.
打开那些门我就可以洞悉你的秘密
Open those gates so I may unlock your secrets
挖掘你的财富
and exploit your riches.
我刚说的很大声吗
...Did I just say that out loud?
我已经等不急想看看
Oh, me sore eyes can't wait to.
女王跟公主了
See the Queen and the Princess.
我打赌她们一定可爱极了
I bet they're absolutely lovely.
她们一定美级了
I bet they are beautiful.
安娜公主?
Princess Anna...?
恩?
...Huh? Yeah?
抱歉要叫醒你 -没事的
- Sorry to wake you, ma'am but... - No, no, no. You didn't.
我起床几个小时了
I've been up for hours.
谁啊?
Who is it?
还是我 门马上就要开了
It's still me, ma'am. The gates will open soon.
要准备好了! -当然了!
Time to get ready. Of course!
准备什么?
Ready for what?
你姐姐的加冕礼
Your sister's coronation, ma'am.
我姐姐的加冕...
My sister's cor-neration...
今天是加冕日!
It's coronation day!
加冕日!
窗户是开的!门也是!
The window is open! So's that door!
他们已经做了如此多的准备
I didn't know they did that anymore.
谁知道我们会有八千盘色拉?
Who knew we owned 8000 salad plates...?
多年以来我一直徘徊在这些空荡荡的大厅里
For years I have roamed these empty halls.
我们的舞厅里为什么没有舞会?
Why have a ballroom with no balls?
终于 他们打开那些门!
Finally, they're opening up the gates!
会有真正的人们到来
There'll be actual real live people
肯定会很奇妙
It'll be totally strange.
但我已经做好准备了!
But wow am I so ready for this change!
这将是第一次
For the first time in forever,
奏响音乐 点亮灯光
There'll be music, there'll be light.
而我也将终于
For the first time in forever,
彻夜跳舞
I'll be dancing through the night.
我是否太高兴得意了一点
Don't know if I'm elated or gassy,
但我就是这么开心
But I'm somewhere in that zone.
这将是第一次
'Cause for the first time in forever,
我不再是一个人 我等不急见到每一个人
I won't be alone. I can't wait to meet everyone...
如果我遇见"他"怎么办?
What if I meet "the one"?
想象一下 今晚盛装出席的我
Tonight, imagine me gown and all.
穿着最迷人的礼服靠着墙
Fetchingly draped against the wall.
美丽而优雅的形象
The picture of sophisticated Grace.
我突然见到了伫立一旁的他
I suddenly see him standing there,
一个美丽的陌生人 高大而白皙
a beautiful stranger tall and fair.
我想要在脸上涂一些巧克力!
I wanna stuff some chocolate in my face!
然后我们畅谈欢笑整晚
But then we laugh and talk all evening,
肯定会很奇妙
Which is totally bizarre.
与我之前的生活迥然不同
Nothing like the life I've led so far.
这将是第一次
For the first time in forever,
充满了魔力 充满了欢乐
There'll be magic, There'll be fun.
这将是第一次
For the first time in forever,
我能被他人注视
I could be noticed by someone.
我知道这肯定会很疯狂
And I know it is totally crazy.
梦到我找到了罗曼蒂克
To dream I'd find romance.
这将是第一次
But for the first time in forever,
至少我有机会!
At least I've got a chance!
别让别人知道 别让别人看到
Don't let them in. Don't let them see.
你是个好姑娘 你必须一直是
Be the good girl You always have to be.
要隐藏 不要感受
Conceal. Don't feel.
好好表现自己
Put on a show.
一失足而天下人皆知
Make one wrong move and everyone will know.
仅此一天
But it's only for today.
仅此一天!等的心碎
It's only for today! It's agony to wait.
等待让人心碎
It's agony to wait.
快让守卫们把大门...
Tell the guards to open up the...
打开!
The gate!
这将是第一次
For the first time in forever.
别让别人知道 别让别人看到
Don't let them in don't let them see
我梦寐以求的时刻终于要来临
I'm getting what I'm dreaming of.
你是个好姑娘 你必须一直是
Be the good girl you always have to be.
一个改变我个人世界的机会
A chance to change my Only world.
隐藏 隐藏 不要感受
Conceal. Conceal. Don't feel.
找到真爱的机会 -别看 别感受 别让人们知道了
- A chance to find true love - Don't See, Don't Feel, Don't Let them know.
我知道明天就会结束
I know it all ends tomorrow,
所以一定要在今天!
So it has to be today!
因为这将是第一次...
'Cause for the first time in forever...
这将是第一次!
For the first time in forever!
没有什么能阻止我!
Nothing's in my way!
嘿 对不起 你受伤了吗
Hey! I'm so sorry. Are you hurt?
嘿!
Hey!
我 我没事 -真的吗
I-ya, no. No. I'm okay. Are you sure?
我刚刚没有看路
Yeah, I just wasn't looking where I was going.
我没事的 -谢天谢地
- But I'm great, actually. - Oh, thank goodness.
哦...嗯..
Oh... Umm...
我是南部小岛的汉斯王子
Prince Hans of the Southern Isles.
我是安瑞戴尔的安娜公主 -公主?
Princess Anna of Arendelle. Princess...?
尊敬的公主
My Lady.
嗨
Hi... again.
噢
Oh boy.
这有点尴尬 你不需要觉得尴尬
Ha. This is awkward. Not you're awkward,
但我们确实..至少我这样觉得
but just because we're...I'm awkward.
你很漂亮 -等等 什么?
You're gorgeous. Wait, what?
我正式的为我
I'd like to formally apologize for
不小心骑马撞上了美丽的安瑞戴尔公主以及
hitting the Princess of Arendelle with my horse...
之后我所有的举措而抱歉
And for every moment after.
没关系的 我不是“那种”公主
No. No-no. It's fine. I'm not THAT Princess.
如果你撞到的是我姐姐埃尔莎 她大概会...
I mean, if you'd hit my sister Elsa, that would be...
你知道的...
'Cuz, you know...
你好
Hello.
还好你撞到的是我
But, lucky you, it's-it's just me.
还好?
Just you?
铃声 是加冕礼
...The bells. The coronation.
我..
I... I...
我要走了
I better go. I have to...I better go.
再见!
Bye!
陛下 手套
Your Majesty, The gloves.
[古挪威语的官方语言]...一些赞颂词...
(formal, in Old Norse) Sehm hon hell drr in-um hell-gum Ayg-num Ok
krund ee thes-um hellgah Stahth, ehk teh frahm fur-ear Uthear...
安瑞戴尔女王埃尔莎
...Queen Elsa of Arendelle.
Queen Elsa of Arendelle.
安瑞戴尔女王埃尔莎
安瑞戴尔公主安娜
Princess Anna of Arendelle!
这么近?你确定吗我不觉得我应该..好吧
Here? Are you sure? I do not think I suppose to...Okay.
嗨
Hi.
跟我打招呼吗噢 嗨
Hi me...? Oh. Um. Hi.
你很漂亮 -谢谢
You look beautiful...Thank you.
你更漂亮一些 不是说你是清洗工
You look beautifuller. I mean, not Fuller.
你不像清洗工 你更漂亮一些
You don't look Fuller, but more beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
派对就是这样的吗
So, this is what a party looks like?
比我想象的要暖和一些
It's warmer than I thought.
这是什么好味道?
And what is that amazing smell?
巧克力
... Chocolate.
女王陛下 这是鼬鼠城的公爵
Your Majesty. The Duke of Weaseltown.
威士顿 威士顿的公爵..
Weselton. The Duke of Weselton..
陛下
Your Majesty,
作为您最亲密的交易拍档
As your closest partner in trade,
看来我邀请你跳第一支舞
It seems only fitting that I offer you.
是再适合不过了
Your first dance as Queen.
谢谢..但我不会跳舞
Thank you... Only I don't dance.
但我妹妹会
But my sister does.
你真幸运 -我不觉得...
Lucky you...Oh, I don't think...
要晕倒的时候让我知道 我会接着你
If you swoon, let me know, I'll catch you.
不好意思
Sorry.
像只灵活的孔雀
Like an agile peacock...
说到这个 能打开城门真是太好了
Speaking of, so great to have the gates open.
一开始干嘛要关上呢?
Why did they shut them in the first place?
你知道原因吗
Do you know the reason? Hmm?
不知道
No. No...
好吧 我们继续
Oh, all right. Hang on.
他们叫我"小北斗星"可不是乱叫的
They don't call me "the little dipper" for nothing.
就像一只 长了猴子脸的鸡 我飞
Like a chicken...with the face of a monkey... I fly.
准备好下一次的话告诉我 我的女士
Let me know when you're ready for another round, M'Lady.
他真是活跃
Well, he was sprightly.
对于一位穿了高跟鞋的男士的确是的
Especially for a man in heels.
你还好吗 -不能再好了
Are you okay? I've never been better.
那就好
This is so nice.
能永远这样就好了
I wish it could be like this all the time.
我也觉得...
Me too...
但是不行
But it can't.
为什么不行? -就是..不行
Why not? If...It just can't.
我离开一下
Excuse me for a minute.
很高兴接住你 -汉斯!
Glad I caught you. Hans!
整个客厅里通常只有我一个人玩..哦 不好意思
I often had the whole parlor to myself to slide...Oops. Sorry.
你的体格起到作用了 我也很肯定
... Your physique helps I'm sure too.
这是什么? -生下来就有的
What's this? I was born with it,
我梦见我被一个巨魔亲过
Although I dreamt I was kissed by a troll.
我喜欢
I like it.
是的 整件事 你了解了!
Yeah, The whole thing! You got it.
等着 你有多少个兄弟?
Okay wait, wait. So you have how many brothers?
十二个哥哥
Twelve older brothers.
有三个认为我是不存在的
Three of them pretended I was invisible...
大概 有两年了吧
literally... for two years.
太可怕了 -哥哥就是这样的人
- That's horrible. - It's what brothers do.
姐姐也是
... And sisters.
我跟埃尔莎在小时候非常的亲密
Elsa and I were really close when we were little.
但有一天 她突然把我关在门外
But then, one day she just shut me out, and...
直到现在我还不知道为什么
And I never knew why.
我永远不会把你关在门外
I would never shut you out.
我能说一件疯狂的事吗
Okay, can I just say something crazy?
我爱疯狂
I love crazy.
我的一生被关上了很多扇门
All my life has been a series of doors in my face.
直到我遇见了你
And then suddenly I bump into you.
我跟你想的一样 因为...
I was thinking the same thing, because like...
这一生我一直在寻找归宿
I've been searching my whole life to find my own place.
大概是派对上的闲聊
And maybe it's the party talking,
也可能是巧克力干酪
Or the chocolate fondue.
但是遇见了你...
But with you...
我找到了归宿
I found my place.
注视着你的面容
I see your face.
给了我与众不同的感觉
And it's nothing like I've ever known before.
爱情是一扇敞开的门!
Love is an open... door!
爱情是一扇敞开的门
Love is an open... door...Door...
Love is an open... door...
和你!和你!
With you! With you!
爱情是一扇敞开的门
Love is an open door.
我说这很疯狂 -什么?
I mean it's crazy. What?
我们吃了彼此的..."三明治"!
We finish each other's...Sandwiches!
我也想这样说!
That's what I was gonna say!
我从没见过如此理解我的人
I've never met someone...Who thinks so much like me.
巧合...多巧!
Jinx... jinx again.
我们的想法如此一致只有一个解释
Our Mental Synchronization Can have but one explanation,
你我注定要
You and I were just meant to be.
告别
Say goodbye.
过去的痛苦
To the pain of the past.
再也不用忍受了!
We don't have to feel it anymore!
爱情是一扇敞开的门!
Love is an open... door!
Love is an open door!
与你在一起的生活能更充实!
Life can be so much more...with you! With you!
爱情是一扇敞开的门
Love is an open... door.
我能说一些疯狂的事吗
Can I say something crazy...?
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
我能说更疯狂的事吗
Can I just say something even crazier?
我愿意
Yes.
不好意思 能借过一下吗
Oops! Pardon. Sorry. Can we just get around you there?
谢谢 她在这里
Thank you. Oh, there she is.
埃尔莎! 我是说..女王
Elsa! I mean... Queen...
我又来了 我向您介绍
Me again. May I present,
南部小岛的汉斯王子
Prince Hans of the Southern Isles.
尊敬的女王
Your Majesty.
希望您能祝福我们的
We would like...your blessing...
婚姻
of... our marriage!
婚姻? -是的!
Marriage...? Yes!
不好意思 我有点困惑
I'm sorry, I'm confused.
好吧 我们还没想好所有的细节
Well, We haven't worked out all the details ourselves.
我们需要几天的时间来计划庆典
We'll need a few days to plan the ceremony.
当然要有鲜汤
Of course we'll have soup,
烤肉 冰淇淋还有...
roast, and ice cream and then...
等下 我们可以住在这里吗
Wait. Would we live here?
这里? 当然!
Here? Absolutely!
安娜...
Anna...
也可以把你的十二个哥哥都请来住...
Oh, we can invite all twelve of your brothers to stay with us...
什么?那可不行
What? No, no, no, no, no.
虽然我们有足够的房间 但是 他们一定...
Of course we have the room. I don't know. Some of them must...
别说了
Wait. Slow down.
没有一个哥哥会住在这里
No one's brothers are staying here.
没有人可以结婚
No one is getting married.
什么?
Wait, what?
能跟你单独说说吗
May I talk to you, please. Alone.
不 无论你想说什么..
No. Whatever you have to say, you...
你跟我们两人一起说
you can say to both of us.
好吧 你不能嫁给一个你才刚见面的人
Fine. You can't marry a man you just met.
如果是真爱的话就可以
You Can if it's true love.
安娜 你知道什么是真爱?
Anna, what do you know about true love?
比你要清楚 你只会把人关在门外
More than you. All you know is how to shut people out.
你请求我的祝福 我的答案是不可以
You asked for my blessing, but my answer is no.
现在 不好意思
Now, Excuse me.
陛下 请冷静...
Your Majesty, if I may ease your...
不行 你该走了
No, you may not. And I-I think you should go.
派对结束了 把门关上
The party is over. Close the gates.
遵命 尊敬的女王
Yes, Your Majesty.
什么? 埃尔莎 不 等下!
What? Elsa, no. No, wait!
把手套给我!
Give me my glove!
埃尔莎 求你了 我不能再这样过下去了
Elsa, please. Please. I can't live like this anymore.
那就离开
... Then leave.
我到底做错了什么?
... What did I ever do to you?!
别说了 安娜
Enough, Anna.
不 为什么?为什么要把我关在门外?
No. Why? Why do you shut me out?!
为什么你把世界关在门外!
Why do you shut the world out?!
你在怕什么?
What are you so afraid of?!
够了!
I said, enough!
巫术 我就知道有
Sorcery. I knew there was
什么可疑的事情在这里
something dubious going on here.
埃尔莎...?
Elsa...?
女王来了
There she is.
陛下!女王万岁!女王...
Your Majesty! Long live the Queen! Queen Elsa...
来跟我们一起喝酒
Come drink with us.
埃尔莎女王
Queen Elsa.
女王陛下?你没事吧?
Your Majesty? Are you all right?
她在那!抓住她!
There she is! Stop her!
离我远一点
Please, just stay away from me.
走开!
Stay away!
怪物...怪物!
Monster... Monster!
埃尔莎!
Elsa!
埃尔莎...
Elsa...
等下!
Wait, Please!
埃尔莎 停下来!
Elsa, Stop!
安娜!不
Anna! No.
海湾
The Fjord.
雪?
Snow?
是雪!
Yes, snow!
你没事吧? -有事
Are you all right? No.
你知道这件事吗 -不知道
Did you know? No.
看! 下雪了!下雪了!
Look! It's snowing! It's snowing!
女王诅咒了这片土地!
The Queen has cursed this land!
一定要阻止她!
She must be stopped!
你得追上她 -等下 不!
You have to go after her...Wait, no!
你也被下了巫术吗
You! Is there sorcery in you, too?
你也是怪物吗
Are you a monster, too?
不 我很普通
No. No. I'm completely ordinary.
没错她是很普通
That's right she is.
以最好的方式
... In the best way.
我姐姐也不是怪物
And my sister's not a monster.
她差点杀了我
She nearly killed me.
你在..她的雪上滑到了!
You slipped on ice...Her ice!
是一次意外 她被吓坏了
It was an accident. She was scared.
她不是有意的 她不是有意造成这一切的..
She didn't mean it. She didn't mean any of this...
今晚错在我 是我刺激了她
Tonight was my fault. I pushed her.
所以让我去追上她吧
So I'm the one that needs to go after her.
什么? 把我的马牵来
What? Yeah. Bring me my horse, please.
安娜 别这样 太危险了
Anna, no. It's too dangerous.
埃尔莎一点也不危险
Elsa's not dangerous.
我会带她回来 搞定这一切
I'll bring her back, And I'll make this right.
我跟你一起去.. 不
I'm coming with you...No.
我需要你帮我照顾安瑞戴尔
I need you here to take care of Arendelle.
是我的荣幸
On my honor.
让汉斯王子来管事!
I leave Prince Hans in charge!
你确定能相信她吗
Are you sure you can trust her?
我不想让你受伤
I don't want you getting hurt.
她是我的姐姐
She's my sister,
她永远不会伤害我
She would never hurt me.
今夜的山林已被大雪覆盖
The Snow glows white on the mountain tonight,
无人进入
Not a footprint to be seen.
这样与世隔绝的王国
A kingdom of isolation.
我才像是个女王
And it looks like I'm the Queen.
大风呼啸 孕育着风暴
The wind is howling like this swirling storm inside.
再也藏不住 天知道我曾多么努力
Couldn't keep it in, Heaven knows I tried...
别让别人知道 别让别人看到
Don't let them in, Don't let them see,
你是个好姑娘 你必须一直是
Be the good girl you always have to be.
要隐藏 不要感受 不要让别人知道
Conceal, Don't feel, Don't let them know.
但是 现在 他们知道了
Well, Now they know.
随心而动 随刃而行
Let it go. Let it go.
反正再也无法隐瞒
Can't hold it back anymore.
随心而行 随心而行
Let it go. Let it go.
转过身 关上门
Turn away and Slam the door.
不在乎闲人闲语
I don't care what they're going to say.
让风暴怒吼吧
Let the storm rage on.
严寒无法再侵扰我
The cold never bothered me anyway.
可笑的是 距离使一切变得渺小
It's funny how some distance makes everything seem small.
曾经控制我的恐惧
And the fears that once controlled me.
再也无法使我困扰
Can't get to me at all.
是时候展现真正的我了
It's time to see what I can do,
突破我的极限
To test the limits and Break through.
不再被规则所束缚
No right, No wrong, No rules for me...
我自由了!
I'm free!
随心而行 随心而行
Let it go! Let it go!
驾驭着狂风与天空的我
I am one with the wind and sky.
随心而行 随心而行
Let it go! Let it go!
你不会看见我哭泣
You'll never see me cry.
这就是我的立场
Here I Stand And...
这就是我的坚持
Here I'll stay.
让风暴怒吼吧
Let the storm rage on...
我的魔力将从天而降
My power flurries through the air into the ground.
我的灵魂随着四周的冰片盘旋而上
My soul is spiraling in frozen fractals all around.
思想化为结晶如一阵冰风
And one thought crystallizes like An icy blast...
我不会再回头
I'm never going back,
过去已成为往事
The Past is in the Past!
随心而行 随心而行
Let it go! Let it go!
我将像旭日搬升起
And I'll rise like the break of Dawn.
随心而行 随心而行
Let it go! Let it go!
那个完美女孩已不在了
That perfect girl is gone.
我站在日光之下
Here I stand in the light of day.
让风暴怒吼吧!
Let the storm rage on!
严寒无法再侵扰我
The cold never bothered me anyway.
埃尔莎! 埃尔莎!
Elsa! Elsa!
埃尔莎 是我 安娜..
Elsa, It's me, Anna...
你的妹妹不是要让你冰住夏天
Your sister who didn't mean to make you freeze the summer.
对不起 都是我的错
I'm sorry. It's all my f-f-fault.
当然了 如果她把秘密告诉我的话
Of course, none of this would have happened
这一切都不会发生
if she'd just told me her secret... ha...
她真讨厌
She's a stinker.
不 回来 不
Oh no. No. No. No. Come back. No.
好吧
Oooo-Kay.
雪 到处都是雪
Snow, it had to be snow,
她怎么会有把整个海湾
She couldn't have had tr-tr-tropical magic
覆盖上白沙的热带魔法
that covered the f-f-fjords in white sand and warm...
火! 啊哈!
Fire! Whoa!
流浪橡树交易站
Wandering Oaken's Trading Post.
还有桑拿...
Ooh! And Sauna...
夏季大甩卖
Big summer blow out.
半价的泳装 目木底鞋
Half off swimming suits, clogs,
还有我自己发明的防晒霜?
And a sun balm of my own invention, yah?
太好了
Oh, great.
鞋子怎么样
For now, how about boots,
冬靴和..裙子?
Winter boots... and dresses?
那会是我们的冬季公寓
That would be in our winter department.
我有个问题 有没有一位年轻的女士
Oh. Um, I was just wondering; Has another young woman,
像是女王这样的人路过这里吗
The Queen perhaps, I don't know, passed through here?
只有你这种疯子才会在这种风暴里乱走 亲爱的
Only one crazy enough to be out in this storm is you, dear.
你和这家伙
You and this fellow... Hoo hoo.
夏季大甩卖
Big summer blow out.
胡萝卜?
Carrots. Hah?
在你后面
Behind you.
好吧 不好意思
Oh, right. Excuse me.
一个真实的七月冰雪呼啸，不是吗
A real howler in July, Yes?
究竟从哪里来的?
Where ever could it be coming from?
北部山脉
The North Mountain.
North Mountain.
一共要四十
That'll be forty.
四十?不 十
Forty? No, ten.
亲爱的 这可不好 看
Oh dear, that's no good. See.
这些是我们的冬季库存
These are from our winter stock,
食物补给严重不足了
where supply and demand have a big problem.
你想知道食物补给的问题?
You want to talk about a supply and demand problem?
我靠卖雪为生
I sell ice for a living.
这可是眼下难做的生意啊
Ooh, that's a rough business to be in right now.
我是说 这可是真的...
I mean, that is really...
真不幸
Ahem. That's unfortunate.
不减价 但我会考虑去
Still forty. But I will throw in a
橡木桑拿看看
visit to Oaken's sauna. Hoo hoo!
嘿 一家子
Hi, family.
我只有十块 帮帮我
Ten's all I got. Help me out.
十块只能用这个
Ten will get you this and no more.
只要你告诉我一件事...
Okay, just tell me one thing...What was
北部山脉上发生了什么?
...happening on the North Mountain?
看起来像是魔法吗
Did it seem magical?
是的!退后
Yes! Now, back up
看我怎么解决这个骗子
while I deal with this crook here.
你叫我什么?
What did you call me?
好了 我是..
Okay. Okay, I'm-Ow! Whoa!
拜拜
Bye bye.
我没有帮你拿到胡萝卜 小斯
No Sven, I didn't get your carrots.
但是找到了一个可以过夜的地方
But I did find us a place to sleep.
免费哦
And it's free.
对暴力致以歉意
I'm sorry about this violence.
我请你吃自制的鳕鱼
I will add a quart of lutefisk,
这样你就不会有坏感觉了
So We'll have good feelings.
只要衣服和鞋子 对吗
Just the outfit and boots, yah?
驯鹿的心比人好
Reindeers are better than people.
小斯 你觉得呢?
Sven, Don't you think that's true?
是的 人类只会鞭打 诅咒 欺骗
Yeah, People will beat you & Curse you & Cheat you.
所有人都是坏蛋 除了你哦
Every one of em's bad, Except you.
谢了老兄
Oh, Thanks, Buddy.
但是人类比驯鹿要好闻一些
But People smell better than Reindeers.
小斯 你不赞同我吗
Sven, Don't you think I'm right?
没错 除了你我都赞同
That's once again true, For all Except you.
好吧 说晚安吧
You got me. Let's call it a night.
晚安
Good night.
别患上冻疮了
Don't let the Frostbite bite.
漂亮的二重奏
Nice duet.
只有你在说话而已
Oh, it's just you.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
我想让你带我去北部山脉
I want you to take me up the North Mountain.
我不喜欢人类居住的地方
I don't take people places.
让我换种表达方式...
Let me rephrase that...
请.. 带我去
Take me up the North Mountain...
北部山脉
Please.
听着 我懂得如何停止冬天
Look, I know how to stop this winter.
我们天一亮就出发...
We leave at Dawn...
你忘了小斯的胡萝卜
And you forgot the carrots for Sven.
噢 对不起 对不起 对不起 我没有...
Oops. Sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't...
我们现在就走 马上走
We leave now. Right now.
抓牢了!我想开快点!
Hang on! We like to go fast!
我喜欢速度感!
I like fast!
把你的脚放下 这才刚漆好
Whoa, whoa! Get your feet down. This is fresh lacquer.
说真的 你是在谷仓里被养大的?
Seriously, were you raised in a barn?
不是 我是在城堡里长大的
Ew. No, I was raised in a castle.
说一下 女王怎么会把冰弄的到处都是的
So tell me, what made the Queen go all ice-crazy?
这 是我的错
Oh well, it was all my fault.
因为我跟一个人订婚了所以她发狂了 因为...
I got engaged but then she freaked out because...
我才刚遇见那个人 在门打开的那一天
I'd only just met him, you know, that day.
她说她不会祝福我们的婚姻
And she said she wouldn't bless the marriage...
等下 你跟一个第一次碰到的人订婚了?
Wait. You got engaged to someone you just met?
总之 我跟她都发疯了
Yeah. Anyway, I got mad and so she got mad.
然后她准备离我们而去
And then she tried to walk away,
我抓脱了她的手套...
and I grabbed her glove...
等下 你的意思是
Hang on. You mean to tell me.
你跟一个刚见面的人订婚了?
You got engaged to someone you just met?!
别分心 关键是..
Yes. Pay attention. But the thing is...
她从来不脱下她的手套
she wore the gloves all the time,
所以我觉得她可能隐瞒了什么
So I just thought, maybe she has a thing about dirt.
你父母没要你注意提防陌生人吗
Didn't your parents ever warn you about strangers?
他们说过...
Yes, they did...
但汉斯不是陌生人
But Hans is not a stranger.
是吗那他姓什么?
Oh yeah? What's his last name?
姓..南部小岛?
...Of-the-Southern-Isles?
他喜欢吃什么? -三明治
What's his favorite food? Sandwiches.
最好的朋友呢? -大概是约翰
Best friend's name? Probably John.
瞳孔的颜色..梦幻般的
Eye color...Dreamy.
穿几码的鞋? -那不重要
Foot size? Foot size doesn't matter.
跟他吃过饭了吗
Have you had a meal with him yet?
如果你讨厌他的吃相怎么办?
What if you hate the way he eats?
如果你讨厌他挖鼻孔的样子怎么办?
What if you hate the way he picks his nose?
挖鼻孔?
Picks his nose?
和吃相
And eats it.
不好意思 他可是王子
Excuse me, Sir. He's a Prince.
男人都这样?
All men do it.
但这些都无关紧要 我们是真心爱着对方
Ew. Look it doesn't matter, it's true love.
听起来不像是真爱
Doesn't sound like true love.
你是什么情感专家吗
Are you some sort of love expert?
不是 但我有朋友是
No. But I have friends who are.
你是情感专家的朋友?
You have friends who are love experts?
我才不信..别胡说
I'm not buying it...Stop talking.
不不 我想去见见这些...
No, no, no. I'd like to meet these...
我认真的
No, I mean it.
嘘
SHHH.
小斯 走!
Sven, go. Go!
它们是什么?狼
What are they? Wolves.
狼?
Wolves?
我们怎么办?我有这个
What do we do? I've got this.
你..别掉下去给吃了就行
You just... don't fall off and don't get eaten.
我想帮忙...不
But I wanna help...No.
为什么不?
Why not?
因为我不相信你的判断
Because I don't trust your judgment.
不好意思?
Excuse me?!
谁跟陌生人结婚了?
Who marries a man she just met?
我们真心相爱!
It's true love!
科里斯托彻!
Christopher!
是克里斯托弗 !
It's Kristoff!
闪开!
Duck!
你差点烧了我! -但我没有
- You almost set me on fire! - But I didn't.
小斯 准备跳!
Get ready to jump, Sven!
你别告诉他怎么做!
You don't tell him what to do!
我来! 跳 小斯!
I do! Jump, Sven!
我才刚买的呢
But I just paid it off.
不
Uh-oh. No, no, no.
抓牢!
Grab on!
拉 小斯!拉!
Pull, Sven! Pull!
我会给你一个新的雪橇和里面所有的东西
I'll replace your sled and everything in it.
如果你不想帮我了我也理解
And I understand if you don't want to help me anymore.
我当然不想再帮她了
Of course I don't want to help her anymore.
事实上 这事摧毁了我
In fact, this whole thing has ruined me.
因为又帮助了人
For helping anyone ever again.
但她自己去的话会死的 -我可以接受这点
- But she'll die on her own. - I can live with that.
如果她死了你就得不到新的雪橇了
But you won't get your new sled if she's dead.
有时我真的很讨厌你
You know sometimes I really don't like you.
准备好 我们来了
Hold up. We're coming.
你们来了?
You are?!
当然了 跟着我吧
I mean, sure. I'll let you tag along.
安瑞戴尔已经被完全冰冻了
Arendelle...It's completely frozen.
但没事的 埃尔莎会解冻这里的
But it'll be fine. Elsa will thaw it.
她会吗 -会的
Will she? Yeah.
来吧 这是去北部山脉的路吗
Now come on. This way to the North Mountain?
这条路比较像
More like this way.
从没想过冬天能这么美
I never knew winter could be so beautiful.
是的..真的很漂亮 不是吗
YEAH... It really is beautiful, isn't it?
但有点太白了
But it's so white.
你觉得 来点颜色如何?
You know, how about a little color?
来点绯红，淡黄绿色...
I'm thinking like maybe some crimson, chartreuse...
黄色怎么样..不 黄色不行
How 'bout yellow...no, not yellow.
黄色跟雪的配搭? 不行
Yellow and snow? Brrrr... no go.
我对吗
Am I right?
嗨!你太吓人了
Hi! You're creepy.
我不喜欢!拿回去!
I don't want it! Backatchya!
请别丢下我 -只是一个头而已
- Please don't drop me. - Come on, it's just a head.
别!
Don't!
好吧 我们的开头不是很好
All right, we got off to a bad start.
呃，身体!
Ew, ew, the body!
等等，我看起来正常吗
Wait, what am I looking at right now?
为什么你们吊在地球上像蝙蝠一样
Why are you hanging off the earth like a bat?
好吧 等一下
...Al'right. Wait one second.
谢谢! -不用谢
Oooh! Thank you! You're welcome.
现在我很完美了
Now I'm perfect.
好吧 差不多了
Well, almost.
好像我的一生都在颠倒中度过
It was like my whole life got upside down.
哦 太重了  对不起 -我只是...
Oh! Too hard. I'm sorry! I was just...
喔!头部冲击!   你没事吧?
Woo! Head Rush! Are you okay?
你在说笑吗我感觉好极了!
Are you kidding me? I am wonderful!
我一直想要个鼻子
I've always wanted a nose.
真可爱 像个独角兽宝宝
So cute. It's like a little baby unicorn.
什么? -嘿!
What? Hey! Whoa.
我更喜欢这样!哈..
Oh, I love it even more! Hah...
好了 让我们结束这件事吧
All right, let's start this thing over.
大家好 我是雪宝 喜欢温暖的拥抱
Hi everyone. I'm Olaf. And I like warm hugs.
雪宝?
Olaf?
没错 我就是雪宝
That's right, Olaf.
你呢?
And you are?
我是 安娜
Oh, um... I'm Anna.
那边那只滑稽的驴是谁?
And who's the funky-looking donkey over there?
是小斯
That's Sven.
那驯鹿又是谁?
Uh-huh. And who's the reindeer?
小斯.
Sven.
他们是... 好吧 这样好理解多了
They're...oh, okay...Makes things easier for me.
哈 他想亲我的鼻子
Ha. Aw, look at him tryin' to kiss my nose.
我也喜欢你!
I like you, too!
雪宝 你是埃尔莎堆出来的吗
Olaf, Did Elsa build you?
是的 怎么了?
Yeah. Why?
你知道她在哪里吗 -是的 怎么了?
You know where she is? Yeah. Why?
你能带我们去见她吗
Do you think you could show us the way?
是的 怎么了?这个怎么用?
Yeah. Why? How does this work?
停下来小斯 专心点
Stop it, Sven. Trying to focus here.
好的 怎么了? -我会告诉你怎么了
Yeah, Why? I'll tell you Why.
我们要找到埃尔莎把夏天带回来
We need Elsa to Bring back Summer.
夏天? 对啊
Summer? Uhum.
不知道为什么但是
Oh, I don't know why but.
我一直很喜欢夏天这主意
I've always loved the idea of summer,
还有阳光，所有的东西都很热
And Sun, and all things hot.
真的?
Really?
我想你大概对热没什么经验
I'm guessing you don't have much experience with heat.
是没有!
Nope!
但我有时会闭上双眼
But sometimes I like to close my eyes
想像夏天来到时会是什么样子
and imagine what it'd be like when summer does come.
蜜蜂嗡嗡叫，蒲公英漫天飞
Bees'll Buzz, Kids'll blow dandelion fuzz.
我会做所有雪人在夏天该做的事情
And I'll be doing whatever snow does in summer.
我拿着一杯饮料，雪白的身体躺在燃烧的沙滩上
A drink in my hand, My snow up against the burning sand.
应该能在夏天晒个漂亮的古铜色
Prob'ly getting gorgeously tanned in Summer.
我将终能看见夏天的气息
I'll finally see a summer breeze,
吹走冬天的暴风雪
blow away a winter storm.
然后发现
And find out what happens to
冰冻的水变得温暖
solid water, When it gets warm.
我等不及要看看我同伴对我的想法
And I can't wait to see, what my buddies all think of me.
想像一下我在夏天会有多酷吧
Just imagine how much cooler I'll be in summer!
炎热和寒冷都是如此的剧烈
The hot and the cold are both so intense,
把它们放在一起，刚刚好啊
Put 'em together, It just makes sense!
冬天是个待在室内相互依偎的好时节
Winter's a good time to stay in and cuddle,
但在夏天我会变成
But put me in summer and I'll be a...
快乐的雪人!
Happy Snowman!
生活困苦时 我要坚持梦想
When life gets rough I like to hold on to my dream
梦中享受那令人放松的夏天艳阳
of relaxing in the summer sun just letting off steam!
天空多么湛蓝
Oh the sky will be Blue...
你们也将会在那里
And you guys'll be there too.
当我终于在夏天做这些冰制物应该做的事时
When I finally do what frozen things do in Summer!
我要告诉它 -你敢?
- I'm gonna tell him. - Don't you dare.
在夏天!
In Summer!
快点! 埃尔莎在这边
So, Come on! Elsa's this way.
让我们去带回夏天!
Let's go bring back summer!
我来了!
I'm coming!
总得有人告诉它
Somebody's got to tell him.
不 你得把树皮朝下
No. No. You've got the bark facing down.
树皮需要朝上
The bark needs to be face-up.
朝下太干燥了
Bark down is drier.
朝上 朝下
Bark up...Bark down.
有人需要斗篷吗
Cloak. Does anyone need a cloak?
安瑞戴尔非常感激你 陛下
Arendelle is indebted to you, Your Highness.
城堡大门开了 里面有热汤
The castle is open. There's soup
大厅里还有热饮
and hot glogg in the Great Hall.
来 把这些传下去
Here. Pass these out.
汉斯王子 难道我们
Prince Hans, are we just
就坐在这眼睁睁看着
expected to sit here and freeze
你把安瑞戴尔的贸易物资通通都送出去?
while you give away all of Arendelle's Tradable goods?
安娜公主下了命令...
Princess Anna has given her orders and...
这是另一回事
And that's another thing,
你渐渐明白了你的公主
has it dawned on you that your Princess
可能跟一个邪恶的女巫串通好了
may be conspiring with a wicked sorceress...
准备杀光我们吗
to destroy us all?
不准质疑公主 她让我掌管这里
Do not question the Princess. She left me in charge,
我会毫不犹豫的
and I will not hesitate to
严惩对安瑞戴尔犯了叛国罪的人
protect Arendelle from treason.
叛国罪?
Treason?!
哇!放轻松点 孩子
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa, boy. Easy. Easy.
安娜公主的马 她怎么了?她在哪?
Princess Anna's horse. What happened to her? Where is she?
安娜公主陷入麻烦了
Princess Anna is in trouble.
我需要志愿者跟我一起去找回她!
I need volunteers to go with me to find her!
我派遣两个志愿者 陛下!
I volunteer two men, my Lord!
做好准备
Be prepared for anything,
你们遇到女王时
And should you encounter the Queen,
就得结束这个冬天
You are to put an end to this winter.
明白吗
Do you understand?
你有什么具体的计划来结束这个冬天吗
So how exactly are you planning to stop this weather?
我要跟我姐姐谈一谈
Oh, I am gonna talk to my sister.
这就是你的计划? 我的冰雪生意就赌在
That's your plan? My ice business is
你跟你的姐姐谈一谈上?
riding on you talking to your sister.
是的
Yup.
你不怕她吗
So you're not at all afraid of her?
我为什么要怕她?
Why would I be? Yeah.
我敢说埃尔莎是世界上最好最温柔
I bet Elsa's the nicest, gentlest,
最热心的人了
Warmest person ever.
看看那个
Oh, look at that.
简直绝望
I've been impaled.
现在怎么办?
What now?
太陡了 我只有一根绳子
It's too steep. I've only got one rope,
你连爬山都不会吗
And you don't know how to climb mountains.
谁说的?
Says who?
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我要去见我的姐姐
I'm going to see my sister.
你会弄死自己的 我不会把脚放在这里的
You're going to kill yourself. I wouldn't put my foot there.
你让我分心了 -或那里
You're distracting me...Or there.
你怎么知道埃尔莎想要见你?
How do you know Elsa even wants to see you?
我现在不能理你因为
I'm just blocking you out 'cause
我要专心一点
I gotta concentrate here.
大多数在山上消失的人都
You know, most people who disappear
是想单独行动的人
into the mountains want to be alone.
没人喜欢一个人 大概除了你
Nobody wants to be alone. Except maybe you...
我不孤独...我有朋友的 记得吗
I'm not alone...I have friends, remember?
你是说情感专家?
You mean the love experts?
没错 情感专家!
Yes, the love experts!
请告诉我快到了吧
Please tell me I'm almost there.
有觉得你那的空气有些稀薄吗
Does the air seem a bit thin to you up here?
坚持住..嘿 小斯?
Hang on...Hey, Sven?
不确定这有没有用但我找到一个
Not sure if this is going to solve the problem, but I found
通向你想去的地方的梯子
a staircase that leads exactly where you want it to go.
哈哈 谢天谢地 抓住了!
Ha ha. Thank goodness. Catch!
谢了!这像是一次疯狂的信任练习
Thanks! That was like a crazy trust exercise.
如果那是冰做的 我可能会哭
Now that's ice. I might cry.
继续吧 我不会评价你的
Go ahead. I won't judge.
好了 放松点 来这边 我抓住你了
All right, take it easy. Come here, I gotcha.
好了伙计 你待在这里
Okay. You stay right here, buddy.
完美无瑕
Flawless.
敲门吧..
Knock... Just knock...
她为什么不敲门?
Why isn't she knocking...?
你觉得她知道如何敲门吗
Do you think she knows how to knock?
门开了 这是第一次
It opened. That's a first.
你们应该在这里等
You should probably wait out here.
什么?
What?
上一次我向他介绍了一个男孩 她就把所有的东西都冰住了
Last time I introduced her to a guy, she froze everything.
但是..好吧 是一座冰之宫殿
But. But...Oh come on, It's a palace made of ice.
冰就是我的生命..再见 小斯
Ice is my life...Bye, Sven.
你也是 雪宝
You too, Olaf.
我? 给我点时间
Me? Just give us a minute.
好的
Okay.
一..二..三..四..
One... two... Three... four...
埃尔莎?是我..安娜
Elsa? It's me... Anna.
安娜?
Anna?
哇..埃尔莎 你看起来很不一样...
Wow... Elsa, you look different...
是好的一方面...这地方..
It's a good different...And this place.
很漂亮 -谢谢
Is amazing...Thank you.
我不知道我可以这样
I never knew what I was capable of.
对于发生的事情我感到很抱歉 如果知道..
I'm so sorry about what happened. If I'd known...
没事的
No, it's okay.
你不需要抱歉
You don't have to apologize.
但你需要离开这里
But you should probably go, please.
但我才来呢
But I just got here.
你属于安瑞戴尔
You belong in Arendelle.
你也是啊... -不 安娜 我属于这里
So do you...No, Anna. I belong here.
独自一人
Alone.
只有在这里
Where I can be who I am,
我才不会伤害到任何人
Without hurting anybody.
实际上 关于这点 58..59..60
Actually, about that...58... 59... 60.
等下 那是什么?
Wait. What is that?
嗨 我是喜欢温暖拥抱的雪宝
Hi, I'm Olaf and I like warm hugs.
雪宝?
Olaf?
你堆了我 不记得了吗
You Built me. You remember that?
你还活着?
And You're alive?
恩..我想是吧?
Um... I think so?
他和我们小时候堆的那个雪人一模一样
He's just like the one we built as kids.
是!
Yeah!
我们曾是如此的亲密
So we were so close.
现在也行啊
We can be like that again.
慢一点...
Slow Down...
安娜!
Anna!
不行了
No, We can't.
再见 安娜... -埃尔莎 等下...
Goodbye, Anna...Elsa, wait...
你不懂 我只是想保护你
No, I'm just trying to protect you.
你不需要保护我 我不怕
You don't have to protect me. I'm not afraid.
请别再把我关在外面了
Please don't shut me out again.
别再关上那扇门
Please don't slam the door.
你我之间不需要距离
You don't have to keep your distance anymore.
因为这一次
'Cause for the first time in forever,
我终于明白
I finally understand.
因为这一次 我们能携手度过难关
For the first time in forever, We can fix this hand in hand.
我们能携手离开这里
We can head down this mountain Together.
不再生活在恐惧之下
You don't have to live in fear.
因为这一次
'Cause for the first time in forever,
我在你身边
I will be right here.
安娜 回去吧
Anna, Please go back home.
你的人生在等着你
Your life awaits.
回去享受阳光并打开那些门
Go enjoy the sun And open up the gates.
但是.. -我知道!你的想法很好
Yeah, But...I know! You mean well,
但是把我留在这
But leave me be.
虽然我很孤单 但是我很自由
Yes, I'm alone. But I'm alone and Free.
离我远点就不会伤害到你
Just stay away and you'll be safe from me.
实际上 并不是这样 -并不是这样是什么意思?
- Actually, We're not. - What do you mean You're not?
你没察觉到吗
I get the feeling you don't know?
没察觉到什么?
What do I not know?
安瑞戴尔被雪深深深深的覆盖了
Arendelle's in deep deep deep deep snow.
什么?
What?
你似乎在全世界下了一场大雪...
You kind of set off an eternal winter...everywhere.
全世界?
Everywhere?
没关系 你可以融化它
It's okay, you can just unfreeze it.
不 我做不到
No, I can't.
我不知道如何.. -你当然可以
I don't know how...Sure you can.
我相信你可以!
I know you can!
因为这是第一次
'Cause for the first time in forever,
我真笨!我不自由!
I'm such a Fool! I can't be Free!
你不需要感到害怕
You don't have to be afraid.
无法逃离我内心的风暴!
No escape From the storm inside of me!
我们可以携手共渡难关
We can work this out together.
我控制不了诅咒!
I can't control the curse!
我们会改变你造成的这场风暴
We'll reverse the storm you've made.
安娜 你只会事情变得更糟!
Anna, Please, You'll only make it worse!
别惊慌
Don't panic.
太让人害怕了!
There's so much fear!
我们会让太阳重见天日
We'll make the sun shine bright.
你在这里不安全!
You're not safe here!
我们携手面对...
We can face this thing together...
我做不到!
I can't!
安娜 你还好吗
Anna. Are you okay?
我还好... 这是谁?
I'm okay... I'm fine...Who's this?
等下 这不重要 你必须得走了
Wait, it doesn't matter. Just...You have to go.
不 我肯定我们能一起解决这事的..
No, I know we can figure this out together...
怎么做?什么力量可以让你结束这个冬天?
How? What power do you have to stop this winter?
阻止我?
To stop me?
安娜 我们得走了
Anna, I think we should go.
不 我不能丢下你 埃尔莎
No. I'm not leaving without you, Elsa.
是，你要
Yes, you are.
停下来 把我们放下来!
Stop. Put us down!
离开这里!
Go away!
小心!
Heads up!
小心我的屁股!
Watch out for my butt!
丢人是不好的!
It is not nice to throw people!
哇 小调皮 冷静下来
Wow, Wow, Wow Feisty pants. Ok, Relax.
冷静 冷静
Just Calm down. Calm down.
好了 我好了
All Right. I'm Okay.
让雪人做它该做的
Just let the snow man be.
我得冷静下来..很好
I'm Calm...Great.
不要吧!
Oh... Come on!
看到没 你让他生气了!
Uh-oh. See. Now you made him mad!
我会引开他
I'll distract him.
你们先走
You guys go.
不 不 不是你们
No, no, not you guys.
这只是让事情变的更困难了
This just got a whole lot harder.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我打到他了!
I got him!
这有一百多英尺深
It's a hundred foot drop.
是两百
It's two hundred.
那是干什么? -我在挖一个雪锚
- What's that for? - I'm digging a snow anchor.
好的，如果我们掉下去怎么办?
Okay. What if we fall?
下面有二十多尺深的新雪
There's twenty feet of fresh powder down there.
会像掉在枕头上一样...
It'll be like landing on a pillow...
希望如此
Hopefully.
好了 安娜 数三下
Okay, Anna. On three.
一...好了 你告诉我什么时候...
One...Okay. You tell me when...
二..我准备好..我一生下来就准备好了!耶!
Two...I'm ready to go...I was born ready! Yes!
冷静下来
Calm down.
三!
Tree!
这什么..哇! 发生了
What the... Whoa! That happened.
哦，天哪，我都变形了
Ah. Ah. Man, am I out of shape.
就这样 嘿 安娜! 小斯!
There we go. Hey, Anna! Sven!
你们去哪了? -我们完全找不着棉花糖了!
Where'd your guys go? We totally lost Marshmallow back there!
嘿 我们刚刚在谈论你
Hey. We were just talking about you.
都是说的好话 都是好话
Ll good things, all good things.
不!
No!
好像没什么作用
This is not making much of a difference! Is it?
雪宝!
Olaf!
坚持住伙计们!快点!
Hang in there, guys! Go Faster!
等下 什么?
Wait, what?
克里斯托弗!
Kristoff!
别回来!
Don't come back!
我们不会
We won't.
嘿 你没说错 就跟摔在枕头上一样
Hey, you were right. Just like a pillow.
雪宝!
Olaf!
我的腿没有知觉了!
I can't feel my legs!
是我的腿
Those are my legs.
嘿 帮我个忙 抓下我的屁股
Ooh. Hey, do me a favor, grab my butt.
哦 感觉好多了
Oh, That feels better.
嘿 小斯! -他找到我们了
Hey, Sven! He found us.
谁是我的可爱小驯鹿?
Who's my cute little reindeer?
别这样跟他说话
Don't talk to him like that.
这里
Here.
没事吧? -谢谢
You okay? Thank you.
你的头怎么了?
Um... How's your head?
没事的 我很好
I mean, It's fine. Ah... I'm good.
哈 我有点头脑迟钝
Ha. I've got a thick skull.
我没有头骨..或者说我没有骨头
I don't have a skull...Or bones.
所以..
So...
现在怎么办?怎么办?
So Now what? Now what?
现在?
Now what?!
噢!我准备怎么做?
Oooh! What am I gonna do?
她把我扔出来了 我不能回
She threw me out. I can't go back to.
安瑞戴尔 跟这里的天气一样
Arendelle with the weather like this.
而且还有你的冰雪生意也...
And then there's your ice business...
嘿 嘿 别担心我的冰雪生意
Hey, hey, don't worry about my ice business...
那担心你的头发吗 -什么?
Worry about your hair? What?
刚从悬崖上摔下来 -你应该看看你的头发
Just fell off a Cliff. You should see your hair.
你的头发变白了 -白了? 什么?
- No, yours is turning white. - White? It's... what?
因为她攻击了你 对吗
It's because she struck you, isn't it?
看起来糟糕吗
Does it look bad?
不 -你犹豫了
No. You hesitated.
我没有 安娜 你需要帮助 好吗 来吧
No, I didn't. Anna, you need help. Okay? Come on.
好的! 我们去哪? -去找我的朋友们
Okay! Where are we going? To see my friends.
那个情感专家? 情感专家?
The love experts? Love experts?!
别担心 他们会解决一切的
And don't worry, they'll be able to fix this.
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
因为我见他们曾做过一次这种事
Because I've seen them do it before.
我觉得我自己就是感情专家
I like to consider myself a love expert.
集中它 控制它
Get it together. Control it.
别感受 别感受
Don't feel. Don't feel.
别感受!
Don't feel!
看 小斯 天要亮了
Look, Sven. The sky's awake.
你冷吗 -有点
Are you cold? A little.
等下 过来
Wait. Come here.
那么 关于我的朋友们...
So, About my friends...
虽说是朋友 对于我来说更像是家人...
Well, I say friends, they're more like family...
总之 我小的时候只有小斯陪着我
Anyway, when I was a kid, it was just me and Sven
直到他们发现了我
until you know, they took us in.
他们发现了你? -是的
They did? Yeah.
并不是想吓唬你 他们有些
I don't want to scare you, they can be
做的不合适的地方..
a little bit inappropriate...
有些吵..非常的吵...
And loud... very loud...
有时有些倔强 还有点
They're also stubborn at times, And a little.
傲慢 而且很重 非常非常的重
Overbearing. And heavy. Really, really heavy. Which you...
但你得知道你会没事的 他们很不错  都是好人
But You know, you okay. They're fine. They mean well.
克里斯托弗 他们听起来很不错
Kristoff, they sound wonderful.
好吧
Okay then...
见一见我的家人吧
Meet my family.
嘿 伙计们!
Hey, guys!
都是石头
They're rocks.
他疯了
He's crazy.
嘿...我似乎认识你 为何会这么重?
Hey, Wow...I pretty recognize you, What's so much weigh?
我一引开他们你就跑
I'll distract them while you run.
嗨 小斯的家人! 很高兴见到你们!
Hi, Sven's family! It's nice to meet you!
安娜 因为我爱你 所以 需要你跑
Anna, because I love you, I insist you run.
我知道你就是情感专家!
Understand you're love experts!
你为什么不逃走?
Why aren't you running?
好吧 我正准备...
Okay. Um... I'm gonna go...
不 安娜 等下!
No, no, no. Anna, wait!
克里斯托弗!
Kristoff!
克里斯托弗的家!
Kristoff's home!
克里斯托弗!克里斯托弗的家!太久了!
Kristoff! Kristoff's home! It's been too long!
克里斯托弗的家!
Kristoff's home!
等下? 克里斯托弗?
Wait? Kristoff?
是的 让我瞧瞧你!
Yeah...Oh, let me look at you!
脱下你的外套 克里斯托弗 我会帮你弄干净的
Oh, take off your clothes, Kristoff, I wash them.
不用了 我穿着就好 听着
Ah! No. I'm gonna keep my clothes on, Look.
见到你们很高兴
Great to see you all.
但是大帕比在哪? -他在午睡
But where's grand Pabbie? He's napping.
看 我种了一个蘑菇
But look, I grew a mushroom.
我获得了一块火焰水晶
And I earned my fire Crystal.
我治好了我的肾结石
I passed a kidney Stone.
克里斯托弗 抱我
Kristoff, Pick me up.
你在变大..是好事
You're getting big...Good for you.
巨魔?他们是巨魔
Trolls? They're trolls.
他带回来一个女孩!
He's brought a girl!
怎么了?
What's going on?
我已经学会怎么应付
I've learned to just roll with it.
我看看你 明亮的大眼睛 小巧的鼻子 坚硬的牙齿
Let me see. Bright eyes. Working nose. Strong teeth.
好的好的 她能帮上克里斯托弗很大的忙的
Yes, yes, yes. She'll do nicely for our Kristoff.
等下 哦不
Wait. Oh. Um. No.
你错了 不是因为这个我才带她来的
You've got the wrong idea. That's not why I brought her here.
我们不是 我不是...
Right. We're not. I'm not...
怎么了 亲爱的?
What's the issue, dear?
你们为什么向他隐瞒这事
Why are you holding back from such a man?
因为他笨拙的走路姿势?
Is it the clumpy way he walks?
什么?
What?
还是他爱抱怨的说话方式? -不是
Or the Grumpy way he talks? No.
还是说他像梨子一样方形
Or the pear-shaped, square-shaped
奇怪的脚? -嘿!
...weirdness of his feet? Hey!
尽管我们都知道他很爱干净
And though we know he washes well
他还是有股怪味
he always ends up Sorta smelly.
但你永远也找不到另外一个比他还要体贴温柔的人了
But You'll never meet a fella who's as sensitive and sweet.
很好  不过
That's nice. but...
所以他需要一点改善
So he's a bit of a fixer upper,
他还有些小缺点
So he's got a few flaws,
有时候他的想法有点独特 亲爱的 比如他和他的驯鹿
His peculiar brain, Dear. His thing for the reindeer.
有点超出自然规律 这说的不是我!
- That outside a few of nature's laws. - This is not about me!
所以他需要一点改善
So he's a bit of a fixer upper,
可我们担保
But this we're certain of...
你只用一点点的爱就能改善他
You Can fix this fixer upper up with a little bit of love.
我们能不谈这个吗!
Can we just stop talking about this?!
我们来这里是因为遇到了真正的麻烦
We've got a real, actual problem here.
我来说...亲爱的你告诉我 是不是因为他跑步的姿势让你害怕
I'll Say...So tell me dear, Is it the way that he runs scared?
或是因为他社交能力低下?
Or that he's Socially Impaired?
还是因为他成天只知道在林子里晃悠?
Or that he only likes to tinkle in the Woods?
我不需要知道这些
I do not need to know that.
你隐藏你的喜欢是因为
Are you holding back your fondness.
他的金发没有男人味?
Due to his unmanly blondeness?
还是他隐瞒自己是最适合的那个人的方式?
Or the way he covers up that he's the honest goods?
他只是需要一点改善
He's just a bit of a fixer upper.
他还有一些小缺点
He's got a couple a' bugs.
我没有
No, I don't.
他的离群是因为
His isolation is confirmation of
他从没尝过安慰的拥抱
his desperation for healing hugs.
所以他需要一点改善，而且我们知道该怎么做
So he's a bit of a fixer upper, But we know what to do.
治好他的固执的方法
The way to fix up this fixer
是和你在一起 就能治好他
...upper is to fix him up with you.
停停停，够了!
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Enough!
她已经和别人订婚了，好吗
She's engaged to someone else. Okay?!
那她也需要一点改善
So she's a bit of a fixer upper,
小事一桩
That's a minor thing.
“订婚”是可以改变的
This quote “engagement” Is a flex arrangement.
况且我也没见到订婚戒指
And by the way, I don't see no Ring.
所以她也需要一点改善
So she's a bit of a fixer upper,
她的思想有点摇摆不定
Her brain's a bit betwixt.
把她的未婚夫踢出去就
Get the fiance out of the way And
万事俱备!
the whole thing will be fixed!
我们不是说你可以改变他
We aren't saying you can change him.
因为人们不会真正的改变
'Cause people don't really change.
我们只是说爱是一种力量
We're only saying that love's a force.
它力量无穷，神奇无比
That's powerful and strange.
人们会做出错误的选择，如果他们
People make bad choices if they're
在疯狂、受惊吓或者紧张的情况下
mad or scared or stressed.
但只要给他们一些爱
But throw a little love their way...
给他们一些爱
throw a little love their way.
你就会让他们做到最好
And you'll bring out their best!
真爱让人做到最好!
True love brings out the best!
每个人都需要一点改善
Everyone's a bit of a fixer upper,
这就是意义所在
That's what it's all about.
父母姐妹兄弟 我们需要彼此
Father, Sister, Brother We need each other
来伴随我们成长
to raise us up and round us out.
每个人都需一点改善
Everyone's a bit of a fixer upper,
但是在紧要关头
But when push comes to shove.
能真正改善我们就是
The only fixer upper fixer that can fix a fixer upper is.
真正的 真正的 真正的 真正的，爱
True, True, True, True, Love.
爱 爱 爱 真爱 真正的
Love, Love, Love, True Love...True-e-e-e-e-e.
安娜，你是否愿意嫁给克里斯托夫
Do you, Anna, take Kristoff to be your trollfully wedded...
等等，什么?
Wait, what?!
你们要结婚啦
You're getting married.
她冷的像冰
She's as cold as ice.
有一股奇怪的魔法!
There's strange magic here!
大帕比!  把她给我
Grand Pabbie! Bring her to me.
安娜 你陷入危险之中
Anna, your life is in danger.
你的心里有一块冰 被你姐姐放进去的
There is ice in your heart, put there by your sister.
如果不拿开的话这块冰会冻住你的心 直到永远
If not removed, to solid ice will you freeze, forever.
什么?不会吧
What ...? No.
但你能帮我移开 对吗
But you can remove it, Right?
我做不到 对不起 克里斯托弗...
I can not, I'm sorry Kristoff...
如果是她的头的话就会容易很多
If it was her head that would be easy.
但只有真爱之举才能融化冰封的心
But only an act of true love can thaw a frozen heart.
真爱之举?
An act of true love?
一个真爱之吻 可能?
A true love's kiss, perhaps?
安娜 我们得带你去找汉斯
Anna, we've got to get you back to Hans.
汉斯.
Hans.
带我们出发吧 小斯
Pull us out, Sven.
雪宝! 来吧 -我来了!
Olaf! Come on. I'm coming!
让我们去亲汉斯吧! -谁是汉斯?
Let's go kiss Hans! Who is this Hans?!
我们是来找安娜公主的
We are here to find Princess Anna.
保持警惕
Be on guard,
女王不会伤害我们的
but no harm is to come to the Queen.
明白吗 -是的
Do you understand? Yes, Sir.
女王
The Queen.
上来这边!快!
Up there! Come on!
请别这样
No, Please.
站远点!
Stay away!
火!小心火
Fire! Fire.
抓住她  抓住她!
Get her! Get her!
埃尔莎女王!
Queen Elsa!
别变成他们害怕的怪物了
Don't be the monster they fear you are.
不..我都做了什么?
No... What have I done?
为什么把我带到这里来?
Why did you bring me here?
我不能让他们杀了你
I couldn't just let them kill you.
但我对于安瑞戴尔是个威胁 找到安娜
But I'm a danger to Arendelle. Get Anna.
安娜还没回来...
Anna has not returned...
请你停下这场严冬
If you would just stop the winter,
把夏天还回来...求你了
bring back summer... please.
你还不明白..我做不到
Don't you see... I can't.
你得命令他们让我走
You have to tell them to let me go.
我会做我所能做的
I will do what I can.
撑住 -快点伙计!
- Just hang in there. - Come on, buddy, faster!
在城堡里面见面!
I'll meet you guys at the castle!
别给发现了 雪宝!
Stay out of sight, Olaf!
知道啦!
I will!
是安娜公主!
It's Princess Anna!
你会 会没事的吗
Are you g-gonna be okay?
别担心我了
Don't worry about me.
安娜!你让我们担心惨了...
Anna! Oh, you had us worried sick...My Lady.
给她温暖  把汉斯王子找来 快
Get her warm and find Prince Hans, immediately.
遵命 -谢谢
We will. Thank you.
保证她的安全!
Make sure she's safe!
我要回去找安娜公主
I'm going back out to look for Princess Anna.
你不能再冒险出去了
You cannot risk going out there again.
如果她发生了任何不测..
If anything happens to her...
如果公主身上发生了任何不测
If anything happens to the Princess,
你就是安瑞戴尔唯一的继承人了
you are all Arendelle has left.
他来了 汉斯王子
He's in here. Prince Hans.
安娜 你怎么这么冷
Anna. You're so cold.
汉斯 吻我.. -什么?
Hans, you have to kiss me...What?
现在
Now. Now.
我们会给你们一些私人空间
We'll give you two some privacy.
到底发生什么了?
What happened out there?
埃尔莎用魔法攻击了我
Elsa struck me with her powers.
你说她永远不会伤害你
You said she'd never hurt you.
我错了
I was wrong.
安娜?
Anna?
她冰住了我的心 只有真爱之举才可以救我
She froze my heart and only an act of true love can save me.
一个真爱之吻
A true love's kiss.
安娜...
Oh, Anna...
这里要真有人爱你就好了
If only there was someone out there who loved you.
什么?
What?
你说过你是的
You said you did.
作为我们王国的第十三个王子
As thirteenth in line in my own
我一点机会都没有 我知道的..
...kingdom, I didn't stand a chance. I knew...
我一定要娶一个女王什么的..
I'd have to marry into the throne somewhere...
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
当然了 埃尔莎是一个完美的继承者
As heir, Elsa was preferable, of course.
跟她在一起是不会有进展的
But no one was getting anywhere with her.
但是你呢 汉斯?
But you...Hans?
你是如此渴望爱情
You were so desperate for love,
你愿意嫁给我 不是吗
You were willing to marry me, just like that.
我想了想 在我们结婚后 我会为埃尔莎
I figured, after we married, I'd have
制造一点小意外
to stage a little accident for Elsa.
汉斯 不 别说了
Hans. No, stop.
可她已经毁了自己 而你
But then she doomed herself, and you were
傻到去救她
...dumb enough to go after her.
求你了
Please.
现在唯一的办法就是杀了埃尔莎并把夏天带回来
All that's left now is to kill Elsa and bring back summer.
你不是埃尔莎的对手
You're no match for Elsa.
不 你才不是埃尔莎的对手
No, you're no match for Elsa.
而我 则是将安瑞戴尔从毁灭中
I, on the other hand, am the hero who is
拯救出来的英雄
going to save Arendelle from destruction.
你是逃不了的
You won't get away with this.
我已经做到了
Oh, I already have.
救命
Please, somebody help.
救命!
Please, please!
我越来越冷了
It's getting colder by the minute.
如果不做点什么的话就会被冻死的
If we don't do something soon, We'll all freeze to death.
汉斯王子 安娜公主已经..
Prince Hans...Princess Anna is...
死了 -什么?
Dead. What...?
她怎么了?
What happened to her?
她被埃尔莎女王杀死了
She was killed by Queen Elsa.
她的亲姐姐
Her own sister.
至少我们念了婚誓
At least we got to say our marriage vows...
在她死在我怀抱中之前
before she died in my arms.
现在毋庸置疑
There can be no doubt now,
埃尔莎女王是一个陷我们于险境的怪物
Queen Elsa is a monster and we are all in grave danger.
汉斯王子 安瑞戴尔听你的
Prince Hans, Arendelle looks to you.
带着沉重的心
With a heavy heart,
我宣布埃尔莎女王以叛国罪将被
I charge Queen Elsa of Arendelle with treason
处以死刑
and sentence her to death.
快!
Hurry Up!
她是个危险人物 动作快些 要小心
She's dangerous. Move quickly and be careful.
门打不开!
The Door not open!
这是什么老兄? -嘿 看着
What is it, buddy? Hey, watch it.
你到底怎么了?
What's wrong with you?
你这样说话我可听不懂
I don't understand you when you talk like that.
啊 停下来!把我放下来!
Ah! Stop it! Put me down!
不 小斯! 我们不会回去!
No, Sven! We're not going back!
她跟她的真爱在一起了
She's with her true love.
什么...
What the...
安娜!
Anna!
救命
Help.
安娜! 不
Anna. Oh no.
雪宝? 雪宝 逃离这里
Olaf? Olaf. Get away from there.
这就是热吗.. 我喜欢
So this is heat... I love it.
别碰它!
Ooh! But don't touch it!
汉斯在哪? 你的吻怎么样了?
So, where's Hans? What happened to your kiss?
我看错他了 那不是真爱
I was wrong about him. It wasn't true love.
那我们不是白跑了?
Huh. But we ran all the way here?
雪宝听我说 你不能待在这里 你会被融化的
Please Olaf, you can't stay here, you'll melt.
在找到能拯救你的真爱之前
I am not leaving here until we find
我是不会离你而去的
...some other act of true love to save you.
你有主意了吗
Do you happen to have any ideas?
爱是什么我都不知道
I don't even know what love is.
我知道 爱是..
That's okay, I do...Love is...
在你需要帮忙的时候帮助你 你知道的
putting someone else's needs before yours, like, you know,
为了救你克里斯托弗把你带给汉斯然后
how Kristoff brought you back here
又离开了你
to Hans and left you forever.
克里斯托弗喜欢我?
Kristoff loves me?
你真的不知道爱是什么东西 对吗
Wow, you really don't know anything about love, do you?
雪宝 你在融化
Olaf, you're melting.
有些人是值得为之融化的
Some people are worth melting for.
可能现在不是时候
Just maybe not right this second.
别担心 我来处理
Don't worry, I've got it!
我们会撑过去...
We're going to get through...
等下 坚持住 我看到些东西
Oh, wait. Hang on. I'm getting something.
是克里斯托弗和小斯 他们回来了
It's Kristoff and Sven! They're coming back this way.
他们回来了?
They-they are?
他跑的很快..呃 我想我错了
Wow, he's really moving fast. Huh...I guess I was wrong.
我猜克里斯托弗不够爱你
I guess Kristoff doesn't love
所以离开你
...you enough to leave you behind.
帮我起来 雪宝
Help me up, Olaf. Please.
不不 你需要
No, no, no, no, no. You need to
靠近火来保持温暖
stay by the fire and keep warm.
我去找克里斯托弗 -为什么?
I need to get to Kristoff. Why?
哦，哦，我知道了
Oh, oh, oh, I know why.
你的真爱之举就在那里
There's your act of true love right there,
像勇士一样穿过海湾
Riding across the fjords like a Valiant,
辛味驯鹿王! 来吧!
pungent reindeer King! Come on!
当心!
Look out!
回这边!
Back this way!
我们被困住了
We're trapped.
滑下去 安娜
Slide, Anna.
成功了!
We made it!
快走...
Go, Go, Go, Go...
快呀 老兄
Come on, buddy, faster.
克里斯托弗!
Kristoff!
小斯!
Sven!
乖孩子
Good boy.
克里斯托弗
Kristoff.
安娜!
Anna!
埃尔莎.
Elsa.
你逃不出去的!
You can't run from this!
照顾好我的妹妹 -你的妹妹?
Just take care of my sister...Your sister?
她从山上回来了 又虚弱又寒冷
She returned from the mountain weak and cold.
她说你冻住了她的心
She said you froze her heart.
我试着去救她 但是太晚了
I tried to save her, but it was too late.
她的皮肤结冰了 头发变成了白色...
Her skin was ice. Her hair turned white...
你的妹妹因为你..死了
Your sister is dead... because of you.
不!
No!
克里斯托弗?
Kristoff?
安娜!
Anna!
埃尔莎?
Elsa?
不!
No!
安娜!
Anna!
安娜.. 不要告诉我你死了..
Oh, Anna... no... no, please no.
安娜.
Anna.
安娜?
Anna?
哦, 埃尔莎.
Oh, Elsa.
你为了我牺牲了自己?
You sacrificed yourself for me?
我爱你
I love you.
真爱之举可以融化一颗冰封的心
An act of true love will thaw a frozen heart.
爱..可以融化..
Love... will thaw...
爱..当然了
Love... Of course.
埃尔莎?  爱
Elsa? Love.
我就知道你可以的
I knew you could do it.
毫无疑问 这是我一生最美好的一天
Hands down, this is the best day of my life...
很可能也是最后一天
and quite possibly the last.
雪宝 坚持住 小家伙
Oh, Olaf. Hang on, little guy.
嘿 我的私人降雪
Hey, my own personal flurry.
安娜? 她不是冻住你的心了吗
Anna? But she froze your heart.
这里唯一被冻住的心是你的
The only frozen heart around here is yours.
我要把这个无赖赶回他的国家
I will return this scoundrel to his country.
让我们看看他的十二个大哥哥
We shall see what his twelve big
会怎么看待他的行为
brothers think of his behavior.
安瑞戴尔感谢你 陛下
Arendelle thanks you, my Lord.
这我不接受
This is unacceptable.
我是无辜的 我只是一个惊恐的受害者
I am innocent. I'm a victim of fear.
我有精神创伤  喔!我的脖子好痛
I've been traumatized. Ow! My neck hurts.
这里有医生吗... -没有?
Is there a doctor I could... No?
我要求见女王!
I demand to see the Queen!
我有一条来自女王的消息
I have a message from the Queen.
安瑞戴尔从此以后永远不会跟
Arendelle will henceforth and forever
鼬鼠城有任何的
...no longer do business of any sort
商业来往
with Weaseltown.
威士顿 是威士顿!
Weselton. It's Weselton!
快来 快来 快来   好的 好的
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on! Ow, Okay, Okay...
柱子   哦 对不起
Pole...Oops. So Sorry.
好的 好的 我们到了
Okay. Okay. Here we are.
我欠你一副雪橇
I owe you a sled.
你认真吗
Are you serious?
是的 这可是最新款式
Yes. And it's the latest model.
不 我不能收下这个...
No. I can't accept this...
你必须收下 不能还 不能换 这是女王的命令
You have to. No returns. No exchanges. Queen's orders.
她正式任命你为
She's named you the official.
安瑞戴尔的冰块总管和运输员
Arendelle Ice Master and Deliverer.
什么?没这个事吧.. -当然有的
What? That's not a thing...Sure it is.
甚至还有杯托哦..你喜欢吗
And it even has a cup holder...Do you like it?
喜欢? 我爱这个...
Like it? I love it...
我真想亲你!
I could kiss you!
我的意思是 我想 我..
I could. I mean I'd like to. I'd...
我能吗我们 我... 我的意思是 我们可以吗
may I? We me... I mean, may we?
等下 什么?
Wait, what?
我们可以
We may.
夏天!
Summer!
你好
Hello.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
我喜欢打开的门
I like the open gates.
我们再也不会关上了
We are never closing them again.
什么? 哦 埃尔莎 它们太美了
What? Oh, Elsa, they're beautiful,
但你知道我不会滑...
but you know I don't ska...
加油 你能行!
Come on, you can do it!
嘿 姑娘们!
Hey, girls!
嘿 伙计们
Hey, Guys
更多精彩 欢迎访问极地影视 www.jddy.net